I want to prove to you that up to 1 dog
can make money
and there bro
and there brother
how are you
this one is Lucas
speaks galera beauty
and he's borrowing me
the dog for us to record this idea come on Kimura
of the time
ah he just won the game
oh you saw my video
well let me tell you this jujuba thing
I will use 1 dog
1 board and 1 slipper
let's see if it will generate 1 connection
and if it will work
follow there
Kiki mess
3rd slipper
since it bursts
come here woman comes
comes love
get 1 whale for you there
thank you
all good
you understand that the owner is here on my side
here or the crowd
all by my side
filtered water
and in a little while she'll have a snack for herself
because she deserves
so it's another creative way
show you how important it is to generate
connection with people
worth my bro
and then people
all good
guy was on a top snack for her here
mine she deserves
how much did you say it is
caraca
the guys here just gave Kimura a Vaseline
valeu hand
thank you for this store
creator's house
this remains there
tamo together valeu
valeu
ehhe